Hubungi

pjenyta@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ jenytaprimaranti (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
HTML5
Microsoft Word

Languages

English (Limited Working)
Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Data, ML, and Al in Google Cloud

Pemanfaatan Al Chatbot untuk Non-Programmer Batch 1

Memulai Dasar Pemrograman untuk Menjadi Pengembang Software

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Infrastructure in Google Cloud

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula dengan Google Cloud

Honors-Awards

Kelompok Terbaik Projek PBO TOP 50 Showcase Story of Time Management

Jenyta Primaranti

Cloud Computing Cohort at Bangkit | UI/UX Designer | Human Relations and Assessor in Coding Class and Coding Festival Area DKI Jakarta

Ringkasan

Hello World! I'm here to connect with people on LinkedIn, so we can learn from each other and share experiences. But, I apologize this is only open to my connections, if you want to join click connect button and become a connection.

Pengalaman

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Cloud Computing Cohort

Februari 2023 - Present (4 bulan)

Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

Bangkit is one of Kampus Merdeka's learning models designed through a technology training collaboration organized by Google, GoTo, and Traveloka which aims to improve technology skills and prepare participants to become future leaders in the technology industry. There are 3 learning paths (Machine Learning, Cloud Computing, and Android), one of them is Cloud Computing which learns about basic concepts, how to build, and manage technology on the Google Cloud. With a great curriculum designed by the Bangkit team, we studied intensively every day and were challenged to create a Capstone Project with a team that included all of the 3 learning paths to make an application. In the end, we got a great reward and a chance to do certification.

Collegawan

Ketua Divisi Content Writer Intern Januari 2022 - April 2022 (4 bulan)

Banyuwangi, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Memimpin, mengarahkan, mengorganisir, dan mengawasi seluruh anggota divisi
- 2. Melaporkan agenda kegiatan, perkembangan proker, dan aktivitas anggota kepada CO
- 3. Berperan dalam mencatat anggota yg aktif maupun tidak aktif, dan juga berhak untuk memberikan poin plus dan poin minus
- 4. Memeriksa laporan kerja Google drive bersama BPH

- 5. Memeriksa sosial media anggota collegawan dan melakukan pembersihan anggota yang tidak aktif
- 6. Memastikan dan mencatat anggota yang sudah maupun belum memberikan feedback sosial media
- 7. Membuat dan mengembangkan design content secara mandiri berupa gambar atas inisiatif saya sendiri
- 8. Menulis berbagai tema yang berbeda untuk kebutuhan website dan caption Instagram yang dilakukan dengan kreatif dan informatif agar memudahkan readers memahami informasi
- 9. Bersama 3 pengurus Content Writer Intern berhasil mencapai lebih dari 20 karya tulis yang telah diabadikan menjadi E-Book

International MUN Official Campus Ambassador Mei 2021 - Juni 2021 (2 bulan)

New Delhi, Delhi, India

This was my first experience join an internship has been a part of such a amazing organization was a amazing experience. I have learned a lot, from international relations to marketing and advertising. I would like to thank the entire IMUN team for providing such a valuable opportunity.

Here is my jobdesc

- 1. Promote International MUN (IMUN) online conference, internship, and membership
- 2. Invite people who want to register IMUN online conference, internship, and membership
- 3. Brand Ambassador of International MUN
- 4. Educate people about IMUN program
- Designed and implemented the International MUN program increasing IG followers by 12.1%
- 6. Collected 1 talents for delegate
- 7. Promoted more than 13 referral codes within 2 months and had an oversubscription of International MUN applicants by 25% by click the link

Pendidikan

Universitas Esa Unggul

Bachelor of Computer Science - B.C.Sc, Information Systems · (2020 - 2024)

SMAN 83 Jakarta

Senior High School, Social Science · (2017 - 2020)

SMPN Jakarta

Junior High School · (2014 - 2017)